A Guide to the William E. Davis photographs, Series 1068 FA463
Rockefeller Archive Center
William E. Davis photographs, Series 1068
1956-1982
Rockefeller Archive Center
Davis, William E.
FA463
6.6 Cubic Feet 15 document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The William E. Davis photographs were donated to RAC by William E. Davis.
Biographical / Historical
William E. Davis served as a contract photographer for Winthrop Rockefeller and family.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: photographs.
Arrangement
As received.
- William E. Davis photographs, 1956-1982; 1068
  - Winthrop Rockefeller
    - Arkansas Opportunity Fund Students (Box 1)
    - Award Recipients (Box 1)
    - Conferences
      - Governor's Mansion (Box 1)
      - Hot Springs, Arkansas with Duke Ellington (Box 1)
      - Regional (Box 1)
      - Republican Governor's Conference with Ronald Reagan (Box 1)
      - Rural Planning (Box 1)
      - Spiro Agnew at the Airport (Box 1)
      - Spiro Agnew "We Will Do More for Arkansas" (Box 1)
      - Winrock (Box 1)
    - Family
      - Anne Bartley, Bruce Bartley, Marjorie Edris (Box 2)
      - Jeannette Edris (Box 2)
      - Wedding to Jeannette Edris (Box 2)
      - Winthrop Rockefeller and Jeannette Edris (Box 2)
      - Winthrop and Winthrop Paul Rockefeller (Box 2)
    - Family Friends
      - Winthrop Paul Rockefeller Friends (Box 2)
    - Non William E. Davis photographs, negatives (Box 2)
    - Parties
      - Christmas (Box 2)
      - "The People of Arkansas Thank You" (Box 2)
      - Press Conference (Box 2)
      - Winrock Scholarship Recipients (Box 3)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller and Richard Nixon (Box 3)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller
      - Candids (Box 3)
      - Informals (Box 3)
      - Portraits (Box 3)
      - Series (Box 3)
  - Arkansas Buildings (Box 4)
  - Winrock
    - Aerials (Box 4)
    - Buildings
      - Exteriors (Box 4)
      - Exteriors (Box 5)
      - Interiors (Box 5)
        - G.W. Atkinson's House (farm manager) (Box 5)
    - Cattle
      - In fields (Box 5)
      - In pens (Box 5)
      - In pens (Box 6)
      - Sales and Receptions
        - 1958 (Box 6)
        - 1959 (Box 6)
        - 1960 (Box 6)
        - c. 1965 (Box 6)
        - 1967 (Box 6)
        - "WR 13", c. 1970 (Box 6)
        - 1976 (Box 7)
        - 1977 (Box 7)
    - Employees
      - Candids (Box 7)
      - Candids (Box 8)
      - Children (Box 8)
      - Picnics
        - c. 1970 (Box 8)
        - 1971 (Box 8)
        - 1976 (Box 8)
        - 1977 (Box 8)
        - 1978 (Box 8)
      - Portraits (Box 8)
      - Portraits (Box 9)
    - Farms
      - Grass (Box 9)
      - Rice and Soybean (Box 9)
      - Rice and Soybean (Box 10)
    - Horses (Box 10)
    - Objects (Box 10)
      - Paintings (Box 10)
    - Series A (Box 11)
    - Series B (Box 11)
  - Winthrop Paul Rockefeller
    - Family
      - Children (Box 12)
        - Andrea Rockefeller: Fourth Birthday (Box 12)
        - Winthrop Paul Rockefeller Jr.: Baptism (Box 12)
        - 1977 (Box 12)
        - 1982 (Box 13)
      - Deborah Cluett Sage Rockefeller (Box 13)
      - Deborah Cluett Sage Rockefeller and Barbara Sears Rockefeller (Box 13)
      - Series (Box 13)
      - Wedding to Lisenne Dudderar (Box 14)
      - Winthrop Paul Rockefeller and Deborah Cluett Sage Rockefeller
        - 1971 (Box 14)
        - 1973 (Box 14)
      - Family: Candids (Box 14)
      - Family: Portraits, c. 1982 (Box 14)
    - Parties
      - Arkansas Traveler Award (Box 15)
      - Arts Center (Box 15)
      - C.S.A. Awards (Box 15)
      - M.S. Meeting at Boat House (Box 15)
      - Ozark Folk Center (Box 15)
      - Reception with Henry Kissinger (Box 15)
    - Unidentified lady (Box 15)
    - Winthrop Paul Rockefeller
      - Candids (Box 15)
      - Portraits (Box 15)